scrapbox.io 2019-03-23

# Scrapbox - Privacy

### A. What This Privacy Policy Covers

Nota, Inc., a Delaware corporation (“Nota, Inc.,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) is committed to ensuring your privacy and protecting the security of your Personal Information. We maintain this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) that summarizes our policies and processes for protecting the privacy of all Personal Information (defined below) gathered from customers, prospective customers, and visitors to all of our affiliated websites, products and services, including, without limitation, [https://scrapbox.io](https://scrapbox.io/) (the “Website”) and all online forms (if any) on the Website used to collect Personal Information (collectively, the “Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services”), and when and how such information is collected, used and safeguarded. This Policy also explains how anyone can review, update, correct, or delete their Personal Information and specify what information, if any, they would like to receive from us on an on-going basis.

“Personal Information” is information about you that is personally identifiable including, without limitation, your name, address, email address, billing address, credit card information, birth date, birth place, mother’s maiden name, gender, zip code, biographical information, ICQ/AIM/Yahoo/MSN/Skype user name, Amazon.com associates code, occupation, industry, and personal interests, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. Please note that any posting made while using the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services is not considered “Personal Information” and is not considered the type of information protected by and subject to, this Policy.

This Policy covers how the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services deal with Personal Information about your children subject to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), and how parents and legal guardians may request from us how they can review, delete or stop the collection of the Personal Information of their child.

Please note that this Policy applies only to sites maintained by Nota, Inc., its subsidiaries or its affiliates, and does not apply to the practices of companies that Nota, Inc. does not own or control, or to people that Nota, Inc. does not employ, control or manage. Moreover, this Policy does not only apply to information collected by us offline.

By using the Website, you are agreeing to the terms and conditions of this Policy. **If you do not agree with any terms or conditions described in this Policy, please exit from the Website.**

### B. Personal Information We Gather

You can access our Website without providing us with any Personal Information. However, we may collect Personal Information at the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services as more particularly described below. Our primary goal in collecting the information described below is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our Website and to deliver better service, products, and more relevant content to our customers, prospective customers, and visitors.

As more particularly described below, Personal Information may be collected from you during exchange of communications relating to the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services. We ask that you provide only your own Personal Information, not Personal Information concerning anyone else. Personal Information may be collected by us and/or our business partners.

The Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services, including future versions, may collect Personal Information when you register, use the particular products or services or post content on any Scrapbox Project as a guest with authoring rights, as applicable.

The Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services may also collect Personal Information when you enter into promotions or sweepstakes.

The Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or others.

The Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services may also collect information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. This information might include information necessary to process payments due to us from you such as your credit card number.

#### IP Address

The Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services may occasionally obtain IP addresses from users depending upon how you access our web sites. IP addresses, browser and session information may be used for various purposes, including to:

  * Diagnose and prevent service or technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.

  * Estimate the total number of users visiting Nota, Inc.’s web sites from specific geographical regions.

  * Help determine which users have access privileges to certain content, services or resources that we offer.

  * Monitor and prevent fraud and abuse.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to use the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.

We use cookies to gather information about our Website users’ browser activities in order to constantly improve our Website and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our web pages in a most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services to better meet the needs of our customers, prospective customers, and visitors.

Specifically, the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services use cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

  * Require you to re-enter your password after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

  * Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services.

  * Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.

  * Conduct research to improve the content and services provided on the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services.

  * Nota, Inc. lets other entities that show advertisements on some of our web pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other entities’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, and not this Policy. Advertisers or other entities do not have access to Nota, Inc.’s cookies.

#### Information Relating to Children

COPPA requires that we inform parents and legal guardians about how we collect, use, and disclose Personal Information from children under 13 years of age. The Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services are not directed at children under 13 years of age but, we recognize that with proper adult supervision some parents might permit their children to visit and utilize the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services. COPPA requires that we obtain the consent of parents and guardians in order for children under 13 years of age to use certain features of the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services.

When your child attempts to register and/or provide Personal Information to Nota, Inc. (including on any of the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services), we require a parent or legal guardian to:

  * Complete the registration;

  * Review this Policy and to verify that the child’s parent or guardian knows about and authorizes our information practices related to children protected by COPPA; and,

  * Verify through the use of an email confirmation and second authorization that the parent or guardian consents to any applicable Terms of Service and this Policy.

Once parental notice and consent has been verified, the information we collect will be treated the same as information collected from any other user of the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services. Without verified parental notice and consent, we will not knowingly collect Personal Information of children under 13 years of age, and if we learn that we have inadvertently collected such information, we will promptly delete it and not disclose or transfer any such information to third parties.

#### How Parents can Access their Children’s Personal Information

In compliance with COPPA, parents and legal guardians may request us to review, delete or stop the collection of the personally identifiable information of their child. You may do so by contacting us by letter, phone or email using the address information provided at the bottom of this page.

If you request that no further information about your child be collected or used, we will be required to terminate your child’s ability to use the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services

### C. Personal Information Use, Sharing and Disclosure

The Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services use information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting.

The Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services do not share Personal Information we learn about you from your use of the web sites, products and services with others except as described in this Policy. We generally do not share your information with unrelated third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We may share, however, aggregated demographic information with our business partners and advertisers. Moreover, the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services may display targeted advertisements based on Personal Information.

When you provide Personal Information through using the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services you are however sharing your Personal Information with Nota, Inc. and its affiliated entities. The use of your Personal Information by these organizations is subject to this Policy.

The Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services may use or share your Personal Information where it is necessary to complete a transaction, to operate or improve the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services, to do something that you have asked us to do, or tell you of products and services that we think may be of interest.

We may also periodically engage in co-marketing activities, where we work with a complementary solution provider to launch a joint marketing program. In these situations, we will only send information to you on behalf of the other; we do not provide your Personal Information to such partner. We may also enter into business partnerships with other parties to provide specific services. If a user signs up for these services or responds to a particular marketing offer, we may share Personal Information such as your name or other contact information that is necessary for our business partner to provide these services or get in contact with you.

Where you are contacted with an offer or service based on information you have shared with any Nota, Inc. Site, Product and/or Service, we will do our best to provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of receiving such further communications at the time you are contacted, however, in connection with any of our paid products and services (i.e., products or services that you license or use for a fee), we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to those products and services, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Nota, Inc. Newsletter, that are considered part of your Nota, Inc. account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

When you create a Scrapbox Project, your user ID or alias that you are posting under may be visible to other users.

When you provide content on any Scrapbox Project, you have the ability to do so in a manner that may include personally identifiable information about yourself.

If you post Personal Information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

The Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services may share personally identifiable information about you under the following circumstances:

  * In the course of operating our business it may be necessary or appropriate for us to provide access to your Personal Information to others such as our service providers, contractors and select vendors so that we can operate the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services and our business. Where practical, we seek to obtain confidentiality agreements that are consistent with this Policy and that limit others’ use or disclosure of the information you have shared.

  * We may share your Personal Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, to establish or exercise our legal rights or, defend against legal claims and if in our judgment in such circumstances disclosure is required or appropriate.

  * We may share your Personal Information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our various terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

  * As we continue to develop our business, we may also sell or transfer all or part of our business. In such transactions, personally identifiable information you have shared with us is generally one of the business assets that will be transferred. The transferred personally identifiable information will remain subject to the promises made in this Policy or subsequent policies to which you have consented.

### D. Other

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Nota, Inc. may revise, modify or update this Policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your particular Nota, Inc. account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. You are responsible for periodically checking our Website for changes to this Policy. If at any time we decide to use Personal Information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will take commercially reasonable measures to obtain consent from you. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your Personal Information in this different manner.

#### Personal Information Storage and Security

We take reasonable precaution to protect the Personal Information we collect from customers, prospective customers, and visitors. When users submit Personal Information via the Website, the information is housed in a secure in-house database in one or more of our offices. The location of our offices may change from time to time and we may acquire offices in other countries at any time. You acknowledge and agree that we may transfer your personally identifiable information to or through any country which may not have privacy (data protection) legislation and regulation comparable to the law of the country in which you reside.

While we strive to protect your Personal Information, you should know that information sent over the Internet, whether by e-mail or by using one of our on-line forms, is not necessarily secure against interception. No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

To prevent unauthorized access, loss, or misuse, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the Personal Information we maintain. We use industry-standard technology, such as firewalls, in an effort to protect the confidentiality of your Personal Information. Moreover, we encrypt your transmission of sensitive information to us (e.g., account passwords and payment-related identifiable information) via SSL (secured socket layer) protocol in the interest of heightened privacy protection and information integrity. Your account information is also password-protected. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.

In addition, only employees who need the information to perform their duties are granted access to personally identifiable information. The unauthorized access or use of such information by an employee is prohibited and constitutes grounds for disciplinary action. Additionally, our information management systems are configured in such a way as to block or inhibit employees from accessing information that they have no authority to access.

Furthermore, our trusted vendors and business partners may be responsible for processing or handling some of the information that we receive. These vendors and business partners are not authorized to use such information for purposes beyond those specified by us and are required to preserve the confidentiality with which we treat such information.

If Nota, Inc. learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services or providing Personal Information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of those sites, products and services. We may post a notice on our applicable web sites if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view the applicable web sites. We may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us at [privacy@notainc.com](mailto:privacy@notainc.com).

#### Changing your Preferences and Personal Information

You can edit your account information with an applicable Nota, Inc. Site, Product and Service at any time. Most Personal Information you may provide is entirely optional. For example, to the extent that parents are considering whether to permit their children to use the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services, we do not condition a child’s participation based upon their provision of any more Personal Information than is necessary to operate those sites, products and services.

You can delete your applicable account by visiting the applicable account deletion page; however, please note that some Personal Information, primarily your contact information, may remain in our records to the extent necessary to protect our legal interests or document compliance with regulatory requirements.

To have access to your Personal Information, you must provide proof of identification such as full name, street address, city/state and zip code, and/or information about your recent activity on the Website. We reserve the right to deny access to any user if we believe there is a question about your identity. And if the burden or expense of providing access to your Personal Information is disproportionate to the risks to your privacy, or if the legitimate rights of others would be violated, we may decide not to provide access to such information.

#### Opt-Out Provision

When we first collect information from you, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of having your Personal Information shared with parties outside of Nota, Inc. (unless otherwise described in this Policy). In addition, if you do not want us to send you e-mail or postal mail about our products and services, you can opt-out at the time of registration or information collection. If, at a later date, you choose to have your name or any other Personal Information removed from our mailing list, you can do so by emailing [privacy@notainc.com](mailto:privacy@notainc.com).

#### Users Outside the United States

We are a U.S.-based company and its business operations are primarily conducted in the State of California. We operate our company and administer this Policy under applicable laws and regulations of the State of California, and the United States. If you use our Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services from outside the United States, you are thereby consenting for your Personal Information to be processed in the United States in the manner described in this Policy. Furthermore, you acknowledge that the privacy laws of the State of California and the United States may differ from the laws in the country where you are located and may not provide you the same rights or protections as those laws.

#### No Guarantees

While this Policy states our standards for maintenance of Personal Information and we will make reasonable efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of Personal Information. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of any Personal Information collected from any Nota, Inc. Site, Product or Service.

#### Links to Third Party Websites

Please be advised that a Nota, Inc. Site, Product or Service may contain certain hyperlinks to other websites. Although these websites may have privacy policies, all of these websites and their privacy policies are independent of our Website and this Policy. We are not responsible for compliance with other websites’ privacy policies or data collection practices. You should review these privacy policies carefully before providing Personal Information to these websites.

#### Contacting Nota, Inc.

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding any Nota, Inc. Site, Product or Service, or this Policy, and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of those sites, products or services, you should complete a feedback form or you can write to us by email at privacy@notainc.com. Alternatively, we can be reached by our postal mail address:

Nota, Inc.

Silicon Valley PAD 1370 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA 94025

Attention: Privacy Officer

If you object to any sharing of your Personal Information that may be permitted under this Policy, you may do so by writing us at the above address. We will take reasonable steps to accommodate your requests as they relate to our advertising practices. In some instances, honoring your requests may interfere with or preclude your ability to use the Nota, Inc. Sites, Products and Services or may require us to terminate our relationship with you.

Effective Date: Oct 1, 2016

Copyright © 2019 Nota, Inc. All rights reserved.
